Trey Helmer

treyhelmer@gmail.com Cumming, GA

Summary:

Experience in creating effective sales strategies, either working directly for upper management and shareholders or as a partner in the project. Detail oriented with excellent communication skills for technical and intangible sales. An effective communicator of "win win" scenarios and business strategies. Charismatic with an Entrepreneurial mindset and driven to make things happen!

Education:

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Ga

Bachelor of Science, Industrial Management, 1998

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Ga

Full-Stack (MERN) Coding Bootcamp, 2019

Business Software Skills:

Slack, MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Visio, Adobe Acrobat, Photoshop, Windows, Mac, Android, iOS, Linux, VOIP, Google Apps for Business, CRM, Zoom, ADP, iRecruiter.

Work Experience:

<u>ClubCorp-Laurel Springs CC</u> - Suwanee, Ga (2017-Current)

Assistant Superintendent

- Scheduling, Payroll, Crew Management, Project Management, Budgeting, Hiring
- ADP, irecruiter

Horseshoe Bend CC/Golf Club of Georgia - Alpharetta Ga (2015-2017)

Team Leader

• Agronomy, Course Renovation and GreensKeeping.

Atlantus Group, LLC/ Atlantus International LLC - Atlanta (2012-2014)

Partner

- Contracted US representative for an emerging brand of Fracking Sands/Proppant Transport and Storage Containers, imported from China.
- Identify new business relationships, JV partnerships and leads in US Shale/ fracking industry.

<u>Dynamic Technology, LTD</u> - Richmond/Atlanta (2011-2012)

Market Research & Development-1 year Contract

- Assisted with the development of the sales/marketing strategy for a new line of Antimicrobial protective products.
- Creative, Branding, Market Analysis and Sales Strategy.

International Alliance Group, LLC - Atlanta, Ga (2008- 2010)

Sales Representative

- Structured sales for various raw and building materials to/from China, Africa, Korea, Brazil and Vietnam. (Bitumen, Sugar, Iron Ore, Proppent.)
- Developed an International network of commodity brokers, reps and agents, utilizing trade portals like Alibiba.com, etc.

M&M Alliance Group, LLC - Atlanta, Ga (2005-2008)

Business Development and Sales Associate

- Helped Develop the Business and Sales Strategies for ViroKlear™, an HIV anti-retroviral therapy, for Africa and Caribbean.
- Generated the lead that secured \$4M initial funding directed towards clinical trial development and market strategies for Viroklear™ parent company.
- Assisted in Business Development for other products, such as the Cancer therapy, Neoplasnet™.
- Engaged The Kemri Medical Institute in Kenya to take part in a special access clinical trial for ViroKlear™.
 (Ref: http://www.kemri.org)
- Assisted with the sale of M&M and its exclusive marketing rights to Australian Investment Company.

Oxygen Infusion, Inc. - Atlanta, Ga (2001-2007)

President/Founder

- Oxygen Infusion provided Medical equipment to Spas and Clinics using Profit Sharing Partnerships.
- Researched trending therapies, negotiated terms with manufactures and negotiated terms with partner clinics.
- Worked directly with Doctors and Clinic Managers to design marketing collateral and campaigns to promote new services created by these technologies.
- Assisted in the design, development and participated as a "proof of concept" franchise model proposed by Bio-telemetric Signaling, Inc. (BTSI) in their public offering for franchised Health Centers for various preventative health regimens.
- Recognized in Atlanta Magazine June 2004.

Global Telelink Services - Dunwoody Ga (2000-2001)

New Market Development Manager

- Global Telelink Services provided proprietary Call Center VOIP technology through their own network, in addition to the operation of their own Call Center facilities.
- Led the efforts to establish additional revenue streams for call centers during intermittent downtime and reported directly to President and Shareholders.
- Designed a plan to offer selected "Seasonal trend" and "Personal Healthcare" products through an infomercial TV format by expanding the capabilities of existing center into an Order/ Fulfillment Center.
- Conducted market and product research with many manufacturers for "first to market" consumer healthcare products.

Lynxus, Inc. - Atlanta Ga (1998-2000)

Sales Associate, Co-Branding/Private Label Division

• Lynxus provided a proprietary-filtered Internet service product to government agencies, Religious organizations, schools and various groups.

- Designed a variety of National Programs for a Private Label Internet Service.
- Designed and Developed the AFSCME (American Federal State and County Municipal Employees)
 PC/Internet bundle for their union members. Recognized by Governor Jeb Bush. The program provided computers and home Internet access to credit challenged State and Municipal employees, through a payroll deduction payment program.

Consumer Expo/ Office World - Marietta/ Atlanta, Ga (1995-1998)

Computer Sales Associate & Technician

• Built, sold and serviced personal computers to retail customers and businesses.

Associations/Programs:

Georgia Tech Varsity Tennis Team Georgia Tech Letterman's Club United States Golf Association

Personal Interests: Golf, Family, Big Green Egg, Georgia Tech Sports, Gadgets, Healthcare Technologies.